<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Benjamin Ellis' blog feed</title>
    <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog</link>
    <description>Benjamin Ellis' blog feed</description>
    <docs>https://cyber.harvard.edu/rss/rss.html</docs>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <generator>Mukudu SimpleBlog Generator</generator>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2017/03/the_tell_it_like_it_is_brigade.php</link>
      <guid>105b3ceacfb3328679756f165887f03e</guid>
      <title>The 'Tell It Like It Is' Brigade - Liars</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There they are, the memes, the statuses and the quotes; &#x201C;Only the truth comes out my mouth&#x201D;, &#x201C;I tell it like it is&#x201D;, &#x201C;You can't handle the truth&#x201D; and all that other  &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mumbo_jumbo_(phrase)"&gt;mambo jumbo&lt;/a&gt;.  Here is a truth, most of those people are lying. I'll tell you why.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2017 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2017/03/buddhism_the_gentle_religion.php</link>
      <guid>5d64bfa3d72998dee4c456e66da8e706</guid>
      <title>Buddhism &#x2013; the gentle religion?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The most famous Buddhist, His Holiness the Dalai Lama whose famous quotes litter social media time lines, is the public face of the peacefulness of Buddhism.  If you were looking to 'find yourself', you might have considered following the thousands of people from the West who head for Buddhist monasteries in the Far East particularly Nepal, Thailand and even &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Buddhism_in_Myanmar"&gt;Myanmar&lt;/a&gt; (formerly Burma).  If you were to be converted, if such a thing exists in Buddhism, you would be joining the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://dhammawiki.com/index.php?title=List_of_Celebrity_Buddhists"&gt;hundreds of famous people who have become Buddhists&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2017/03/capita_symbol_of_what_is_wrong_with_capitalism.php</link>
      <guid>86b68d1bc6b2999aa0f5d2df3135b42c</guid>
      <title>Capita &#x2013; Symbol Of What Is Wrong With Capitalism?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Capita, somewhat unlovingly called C*apita by mostly ex-employees of whom I am one (ex-employee that is), reports a &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.ft.com/content/45b27fe2-ff22-11e6-8d8e-a5e3738f9ae4"&gt;33 per cent drop in pre-tax profits as it loses its chief executive Andy Parker&lt;/a&gt;.  After 3 years in charge, Mr Parker joins the additional 2,000 job losses announced in &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.ft.com/content/ec0ab330-bd16-11e6-8b45-b8b81dd5d080"&gt; December after the second profits warning&lt;/a&gt;.  To further cut Capita&#x2019;s 69,000 staff headcount by about 3 per cent, plans are afoot to send some jobs to India - not the 1st time &#x2013; and &#x201C;introduce robotics and automation to parts of the business&#x201D; amid another restructure.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2017/03/love_is_not_enough.php</link>
      <guid>e009f72d1917f2b8480d6ead3d571017</guid>
      <title>Love is not enough.</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&#x266B;&#x266A;&#x266B;&#x266A;&#x266B;&lt;em&gt;Bitter-sweet memories, that's all I have, and all I'm taking with me. Good-bye, oh, please don't cry, cause we both know that I'm not what you need and &#x2026; I will always love you...&lt;/em&gt;&#x266B;&#x266A;&#x266B;&#x266A;&#x266B;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2017/02/customer_care_british_style.php</link>
      <guid>2e7e30b811ffb340ef0247c32fca4653</guid>
      <title>Customer Care - British Style.</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Since I am now over the age of 50, I am now part of the army of grumpy old men and bear my responsibility to complain with all that great British fortitude.  Several incidents in the last few weeks have left me feeling that I need to have have a word about British customer care, so don't scroll past.   I know that dealing with the public can be trying at the best of times &#x2013; see this post &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://itsfeliciajuliana.com/nightmare-clients-customers/"&gt;Nightmare Clients And Customers&lt;/a&gt; about the matter but I digress.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2017/02/being_setup_for_a_cheap_takeover.php</link>
      <guid>f35dd14df668b5ca8a3effe7a8f75c17</guid>
      <title>Is Our Bank Being Setup for A Cheap Takeover?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Politicians are good at deflection &#x2013; when they want us to get mad, they tell us its our money &#x2013; as in immigrants are claiming your money &#x2013; and when they want us not to take notice they say the government's money &#x2013; as in the 'government' owned bank RBS &#x2013; Royal Bank of Scotland.  Working as a civil servant many years ago in Zimbabwe, one lesson I learnt was that the government does not have any money, we, the people or specifically the tax payers, trust the government to spend our money.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2017 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2017/02/lost_my_religion.php</link>
      <guid>d07de6fde4f540b38ce84c913ca71718</guid>
      <title>Somehow, I Lost My Religion.</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Well that is not exactly true.  Religion, as most know it, that I lost many, many years ago.  What I am actually talking about is my spirituality.  Confused?  I will elaborate.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2017/02/that_time_again.php</link>
      <guid>acb698dc99c2179711f4e3c69a031b61</guid>
      <title>That Time Again</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No trumpets sound when the important decisions of our life are made. Destiny is made known silently. - Agnes de Mille (1909 &#x2013; 1993)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2017/01/a_mexican_lesson_of_all_eggs_in_one_basket_for_us.php</link>
      <guid>6a7fe4ce792b81fb066fdb8bd7896a08</guid>
      <title>A Mexican Lesson Of 'All Eggs in one basket' For Us.</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the hardest lessons my colleagues and I learnt when we were running our small business was that it was a mistake to have one of your customers provide most of your income.  This meant that we bent over backwards, sometimes to our own detriment, to ensure we kept their business.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2017/01/plastic_carrier_bag_charge_wasted_opportunity.php</link>
      <guid>1a128bcec690cfdebbfb998a7828ff1e</guid>
      <title>Plastic Carrier Bag Charge &#x2013; Wasted Opportunity (#5p2recycle)</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My local Tesco supermarket in their wisdom no longer provide plastic carrier bag recycling facilities.  Facilities were removed 'since the 5 pence bag charge was introduced'.  Following the example of &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.bigfatbags.co.uk/bans-taxes-charges-plastic-bags/"&gt;many other countries&lt;/a&gt;, on 5th October 2015, England introduced 5 pence &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.gov.uk/government/collections/carrier-bags"&gt;charges for single-use plastic carrier bags&lt;/a&gt;.  Now maybe I should have taken more notice when the the charge was introduced but I assumed that the charge would go into 'plastic carrier bag' recycling facilities considering that only retailers with more than 250 employees are obliged to charge for bags.  This leaves tens of thousands of shops &#x2013; many in inner city areas &#x2013; that still do not charge for carrier bags.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2017 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2017/01/why_i_fear_writing_again.php</link>
      <guid>3d32a98358e0bc7b780f76f10b5ed902</guid>
      <title>Why I Fear Writing Again</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Isn't funny that societies that historically measured the level of their 'civilisation'  based on their artistic appreciation and artistic creation, that in this day and age most all types of artists in the developed world have to hold down day jobs to make ends meet?  Only a small fraction actually make any real money.  The picture is what my second eldest child and daughter bought me as my present for my 50th birthday.  I'm not sure but I may have inspired her choice of present by discussing my writing and other artistic issues at some point.  &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2017/01/universal_basic_income.php</link>
      <guid>3e578a2c9ac650d1adeaaf3dcf665dd1</guid>
      <title>Universal Basic Income</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week's big new story is Oxfam's report on how the &lt;a href="http://oxfam.org.uk/media-centre/press-releases/2017/01/eight-people-own-same-wealth-as-half-the-world" target="_blank"&gt;eight people own same wealth as half the world&lt;/a&gt;. Last year it was &lt;a href="http://www.oxfam.org.uk/media-centre/press-releases/2016/01/62-people-own-same-as-half-world-says-oxfam-inequality-report-davos-world-economic-forum" target="_blank"&gt;62 people&lt;/a&gt;! The principle of 'Universal Basic Income' appears to be the idea that appears to be able to provide a workable solution against widespread poverty especially in countries where the 'extended family' support structures, important in poorer societies, have been eroded over the recent past generations.  &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2017/01/expectations_and_disappointments.php</link>
      <guid>532b3cf915d0dd18795e1ba490ad7d07</guid>
      <title>Expectations and Disappointments</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;"That's it, I'm done, from now on I will look after number one, me and mine."&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2017/01/resolutions_resolved.php</link>
      <guid>6a2ce5417018a74f06cdb59dfd2e2de1</guid>
      <title>Resolutions resolved.</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Many years ago, at least over 25 years ago, my mother who was a 60 a day smoker at the time decided to stop smoking on New Year's day.  I had never known my Mum to make a resolution before nor I cannot remember her doing it since.  Many people will discourage you from making resolutions by saying why wait for New Year's day to make a change that you should make at the time you decide you need the change.  I would argue that there is something memorable about the date &#x2013; the 1st of January - that makes it special.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2015/06/geotagging_photos.php</link>
      <guid>ed75e2d24d153acd98bb778b0c50e1ba</guid>
      <title>Geo-tagging Photographs</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Recently I have been trying to get all the photographs I have taken over the last few years organised and shared on the web.  The need to easily share the photographs led me to develop a simple PHP web based photo gallery browser which you can find &lt;A HREF="https://github.com/bencellis/simplephotobrowser"&gt;here&lt;/A&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2015 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/09/racial-identity-and-happiness.php</link>
      <guid>64c7ddaf752b079d78ff68ce0f0e9d13</guid>
      <title>Racial Identity and Happiness</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I want to let you in on something. My new project that has been keeping me from posting here as often as I should and want is called &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.mixedindifferentshades.net/" target="_blank"&gt;'Mixed In Different Shades'&lt;/a&gt; and is about the history of inter-cultural relationships and mixed heritage people around the world. How are these two things related you might ask, a blog dealing with trying to find happiness and a history of various small populations around the world? Let me explain.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/09/mixed-history-in-the-making.php</link>
      <guid>0e309182358f394b69f25a1d5fa3d943</guid>
      <title>'Mixed' History In The Making</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A recent &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.geog.leeds.ac.uk/fileadmin/downloads/school/research/projects/migrants/WP_ETH_POP_PROJECTIONS.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;study by Leeds University &lt;/a&gt;that spawned a score of news stories (&lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/10607480" target="_blank"&gt;BBC&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.guardian.co.uk/uk/2010/jul/13/uk-population-growth-ethnic-minorities" target="_blank"&gt;Guardian&lt;/a&gt;) estimated that numbers of ethnic minorities in the UK will grow from 8 to 20 per cent of the population in 2051.&#xA0; Apart from the 'other white' ethnic group which will be the fuelled by expected high levels of immigration from Europe, Australasia and the US, the percentage of people identifying themselves as being of 'mixed race' is expected to grow substantially.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/09/if-this-is-the-new-entrepreneur-were-in-trouble.php</link>
      <guid>a8024115f6337569e260c5e355490482</guid>
      <title>If This Is The New Entrepreneur, We're In Trouble</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Having recently moved for being principally a web developer working on software that allowed educators to create, manage and distribute content to being a content creator and distributor directly to consumers, I have become aware of a new type of rapidly growing internet entrepreneur, the marketer.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/09/worry-about-our-education-sector.php</link>
      <guid>5bcbe250488f2dc5a4813786d6ded6a4</guid>
      <title>Worry About Our Education Sector</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My daughter just came back from her old college where she had been asked by them to attend to request a letter confirming her leaving date.&#xA0; The letter is required by the Job Centre and you would expect it is a common request by ex-college students.&#xA0; She was told it would take up to 2 weeks to have the letter issued.&#xA0; Considering that fact that the letter is usually required by other bureaucrats to allow some to for example, sign on as unemployed, you would think they would have their act together.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/09/money-can-buy-you-happiness.php</link>
      <guid>211b6fe4ff872c51f885767bfe2068e0</guid>
      <title>Money can buy you happiness</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CAN money buy you happiness? The answer, it appears, depends on what you mean by "happiness". High earners are generally more satisfied with their lives, it seems, but a persons day-to-day emotional wellbeing is only influenced by money up to a certain point.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/08/china-and-india-will-make-the-west-poorer.php</link>
      <guid>5c136f3149f73b15c5d1f1ee88ed3f57</guid>
      <title>China and India will make the west poorer?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;"The current financial crisis could bring about a change in the international economic order with countries like China and India becoming the dominant global economic powers."&#xA0;&#xA0; The Chief Economist of one of the world's biggest banks, HSBC, believes Asia's rise poses a threat to prosperity in the West.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/08/junk-food-drugs.php</link>
      <guid>1cb766b90ba33815b223dce81e117ece</guid>
      <title>Junk Food &amp;amp; Drugs</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Fast food outlets should hand out&#xA0; a statin pill, a&#xA0;cholesterol-lowering drug, to customers to combat the effects of fatty food, say an&#xA0;Imperial College London team.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/07/dancing-happiness.php</link>
      <guid>07eed4dc2bd8965e25c878b8201b341c</guid>
      <title>Dancing Happiness</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;When you get the choice to sit it out or dance, I hope you dance. [Lee Ann Womack - I Hope You Dance*]&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/07/rent-a-friend-week.php</link>
      <guid>fc9bbd93b4e3938b8a633bba510b3980</guid>
      <title>Rent A Friend Week</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&#x201C;I am available on most weeknights, not degree educated but well versed in matters of politics, economics, religion and the like. Personal disasters like career disappointments and failed romantic encounters can be discussed and I am not too averse to bouncing balls, kicking balls and hitting balls with a bat but much prefer the kind of play available at the local night club. I can hold my liquor quite well and am unlikely to return any curries eaten under the influence. Being a little on the large side enables me to fireman lift any friend to whom the excitement becomes too much. All this for the price of a taxi ride home! Bookings being take now, form an orderly queue please, we&#x2019;re British.&#x201D;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/07/racism-tribalism-classism-prejudice-without-substance.php</link>
      <guid>e0c9560f592186493471f01df5122d93</guid>
      <title>Racism, Tribalism, Classism - Prejudice without Substance</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My 60 year plus mother holds some very set view about certain sections of society that may have some basis in experience but most likely does not. Since she comes for the generation of the great &#x2013;isms, I assumed that my siblings and I just brushed off these prejudices, sometimes with argument. Imagine my surprise when discussing a certain serious family issue with one of my siblings when they strongly expressed an opinion consistent with one of my mother&#x2019;s which I know is not based in their experience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/07/ambition-when-family-is-not-enough.php</link>
      <guid>5407cd8c8a79a90e8d2a380dd88b427a</guid>
      <title>Ambition - When Family Is Not Enough....</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Unlike many of my peers, when I was in my middle teenage years, I knew that I wanted to have a family; I wanted to be a father. I was going to find the right woman, get married, have babies and have a good job to support it all. I knew this because I loved children, loved being amongst families, mostly other people&#x2019;s, having had no real &#x2018;family&#x2019; experience or so I thought at the time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/07/the-changing-face-of-marriage.php</link>
      <guid>877fd0ae00ceb6c9b211363297de2231</guid>
      <title>The Changing Face Of Marriage</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We do not need to look for &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Divorce_rate" target="_blank"&gt;statistics&lt;/a&gt; to prove that the rate of marriage breakdowns is growing. Many of us have many have experienced it ourselves or have close family and friends who have and those of us with children will know that a significant proportion of their classmates come from &#x2018;broken homes&#x2019;. Some of those classmates will come from &#x2018;single parent&#x2019; families where a marriage was never entered into in the first place but may have been a co-habitation or &#x2018;break-up before marriage&#x2019; scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/07/when-the-oppressed-become-the-oppressors.php</link>
      <guid>7a8e4118fd5f5dd6f00b332f3ce6b87d</guid>
      <title>When The Oppressed Become The Oppressors</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&#x201C;Set me free so that I may do to others what you did to me.&#x201D;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/07/the-simple-things.php</link>
      <guid>a37e2d44e098a19f04fb1e065dfa6318</guid>
      <title>The Simple Things....</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here is one man's view of how the simple, not necessarily the easy, can make you happy.&#xA0; &#xA0;Though written from the sense of the simple home in the Brazilian favelas compared to the high life in the USA, it is the emphasis on simplicity, difficulty and community that the sense of wellbeing is being found - &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://lifeinrocinha.blogspot.com/2009/05/what-is-home.html"&gt;What is Home?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/07/xxx-iting-fundraising.php</link>
      <guid>706d60ab585995548baebd0eb4d084ee</guid>
      <title>XXX-iting Fundraising</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A "big budget" pornographic film was shot in a London hospital when it hired out one of its wards to a film company.&#xA0; The movie generated "substantial income" for the hospital, Conservative MP Penny Mordaunt said &#xA0;&lt;a target="_blank" href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/england/london/10518917.stm"&gt;BBC News - 'Big budget' porn film shot in London hospital&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/07/people-died-for-this.php</link>
      <guid>968586a0a747de0a4832d115586f0d88</guid>
      <title>People Died For This!</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;"MPs in Kenya have voted to boost their own salaries, making them among the world&#x2019;s best paid politicians."&#xA0; &lt;a href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/africa/10476388.stm" target="_blank"&gt;http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/africa/10476388.stm&lt;/a&gt;.&#xA0; Apparently 'the vote has provoked anger from the general public and the media, correspondents say'.&#xA0; Well I&#x2019;m not surprised.&#xA0; The Kenyan PM will earn more than the Uk Premier and the US President and this is a third world country with much lower costs of living.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/07/kenya-nairobi-ranked-among-most-expensive-cities.php</link>
      <guid>efa682999e11692434c5c7e0759f1a35</guid>
      <title>Nairobi - One Of The Most Expensive Cities</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nairobi has made it into the list of the worlds most expensive cities for expatriates, according to a new survey.&#xA0; The continued slide in the Nairobis ranking, experts warn, could make the East Africas hub less attractive to international workers.The cost of living index compiled by Mercer, an international human resource consultancy, has ranked the city at position 88 of the most expensive cities in the world-- the first time it has made it to the list of the top 100. It was ranked at no. 114 last year, meaning it has dropped 26 places to edge closer to the most costly city among the 214 polled. (&lt;a target="_blank" href="http://allafrica.com/stories/201006301118.html"&gt;allAfrica.com: Kenya: Nairobi Ranked Among Most Expensive Cities&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/06/hate-fathers-day.php</link>
      <guid>9a41689e6fbd2b2ccb1ef6945c591a0c</guid>
      <title>Hate Father&#x2019;s Day.</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Father's_Day"&gt;Father&#x2019;s Day&lt;/a&gt; (at least in most parts of the world) , one of the popular hashtags on Twitter was #FuckFathersDay and a search of the words &#x2018;hate&#x2019; and &#x2018;father&#x2019; or &#x2018;daddy&#x2019; would have displayed a frighteningly growing results list.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/06/british-firms-buy-chiadzwa-blood-diamonds.php</link>
      <guid>9f74f37cd66c18c5dcce23e3cc14d477</guid>
      <title>British Firms Buy Chiadzwa 'Blood' Diamonds</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;British and Belgian companies have been buying diamonds from the Chiadzwa fields while their governments claim the gems are "bloody" and Zimbabwe should not be given Kimberley Process Certification to export them see &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://allafrica.com/stories/201006180051.html"&gt;allAfrica.com: Zimbabwe: British Firms Buy Chiadzwa Diamonds&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/06/msp-quits-over-attractive-girl-remark.php</link>
      <guid>80789397bbba18d16c7158c04ed4248a</guid>
      <title>MSP quits over 'attractive girl' remark</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;"To be blunt, it is the job of the convener to ensure his committee is running smoothly and efficiently - not to ogle members of the audience." Brian Taylor,Political editor, BBC Scotland &lt;a target="_bkank" href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/scotland/10332299.stm"&gt;BBC News - Frank McAveety quits over 'attractive girl' remark&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/06/get-a-life-it-is-the-world-cup.php</link>
      <guid>651403bb1e848125697cb8991678db50</guid>
      <title>Get A Life, It Is The World Cup!</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;"Allowing people to take time out to watch football during working hours is simply too costly, untimely, and unfair," so says Willem Smit, a researcher at the Institute for Management Development (IMD) in Switzerland. Smit has reckoned that if just half the workforce in contending nations knocks off to cheer their side on during the World Cup games, the cost to the global economy could be $10.4 billion in lost production time alone - &lt;a href="http://services.newsweek.com/id/238697" target="_blank"&gt;Soccer&#x2019;s Bad Influence on Brazil&lt;/a&gt; (notice the soccer reference in the title).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/06/headline-figures-dont-make-happy-people.php</link>
      <guid>5a0046623e29b07837a6ac8f0e643ed8</guid>
      <title>Headline Figures Don't Make Happy People</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Exactly who are these people? Who are these analysts, forecasters and experts that come up with this kind of talk that dominates our news stories?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/06/some-things-were-better-under-apartheid.php</link>
      <guid>f81946916bf08dc4136ebd450ab883c4</guid>
      <title>&#x201C;Some Things Were Better Under Apartheid&#x201D;</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ian Smith , rebel leader of then Rhodesia, was reported to take great delight in telling all and sundry about the fact that many Zimbabwean &#x2018;Africans&#x2019; he met told him that life was better under his regime than under the new independent Zimbabwe. In a mirror sentiment, BBC correspondent, Hugh Sykes discovers that some in post apartheid South Africa (&lt;a href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/programmes/from_our_own_correspondent/8711089.stm" target="_blank"&gt;BBC News - 'Some things were better under apartheid'&lt;/a&gt;) hold a similar view.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/06/money-talks-aid-saves-gays-in-malawi.php</link>
      <guid>cc424770675c08c8c1ebb28a0cf006fd</guid>
      <title>Money Talks: Aid Saves Gays in Malawi</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Malawi President Bingu wa Mutharika has admitted that he pardoned a gay couple sentenced to 14 years because he was concerned about international aid (&lt;a href="http://allafrica.com/stories/201006020834.html" target="_blank"&gt;allAfrica.com: Malawi: Mutharika Pardoned Gays Because He Was Worried About Aid&lt;/a&gt;). I have nothing against gays, if 2 adult same gender persons wish to get it on, so be it. However, many of us are very aware that many stories do not make the news, we know not every murder, every child abduction, every shooting or stabbing or even every pit-bull ravished child makes it to the headlines and so what happens to the other gays that may be languishing in Malawi, carrying out &#x2018;sodomy&#x2019; acts, will they get pardoned too? Will they avoid prosecution?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/06/lighting-woes-funny-world.php</link>
      <guid>0a7c28ddc6524865d0d1027eb91863a4</guid>
      <title>Lighting Woes - Funny World</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As Swansea council have decided to switch off around 1,500 street lights in in search of savings up to &#xA3;100,000 a year (&lt;a href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/wales/south_west_wales/10213003.stm" target="_blank"&gt;BBC News - Swansea Council begins street light cut backs&lt;/a&gt;), Cape Town in South Africa&#x2019;s city bosses are to keep the lights on round the clock to deter thieves of a surging crime wave involving the theft of electricity cables blighting the city (&lt;a href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/africa/8714734.stm" target="_blank"&gt;Cape Town lights stay on in daylight to deter theft&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/06/africa-must-find-its-way-out-of-poverty.php</link>
      <guid>d8aa3068a7a25e8c7120071f0817ea0a</guid>
      <title>Africa Must Find Its Way Out Of Poverty</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Namibia&#x2019;s Bishop Zephania Kameeta recently said "the poor and unemployed, who make up half of the Namibian population, still cannot believe that President Pohamba said we cannot dish out money for free to people who do nothing." The bishop was commenting on Namibia&#x2019;s President's comments on the Basic Income Grant (see &lt;a href="http://allafrica.com/stories/201005170143.html" target="_blank"&gt;allAfrica.com: Namibia: A Way Forward for Big Initiative&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/05/does-science-need-its-dissidents.php</link>
      <guid>1ba9e93c156c01f6fbd130eeee7108e2</guid>
      <title>Does Science Need its Dissidents?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dr Andrew Wakefield, the doctor who first suggested a link between MMR vaccinations and autism, acted "dishonestly and irresponsibly", the official medical regulator found and has guilty of serious professional misconduct. Dr Wakefield has subsequently been struck off the medical register. (see &lt;a href="http://www.guardian.co.uk/society/2010/may/24/mmr-doctor-andrew-wakefield-struck-off" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.guardian.co.uk/society/2010/may/24/mmr-doctor-andrew-wakefield-struck-off&lt;/a&gt;). Dr Wakefield still stands by his findings and has vowed to continue the fight.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/05/capitalist-morals-needed.php</link>
      <guid>cf8604c755d643c53393cad699306e24</guid>
      <title>Capitalist Morals Needed</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The financial crisis in Greece has lead to the &lt;a href="http://www.guardian.co.uk/commentisfree/2010/may/09/greece-speculators-eurozone" target="_blank"&gt;expectation&lt;/a&gt; that the vultures are circling ready to make fortunes the like not seen since &lt;a href="http://www.georgesoros.com/" target="_blank"&gt;George Soros&lt;/a&gt; socked it to the bank of England on Black Wednesday in 1992. The vultures are not expected to show any mercy to the thousands who will lose jobs and houses and pensions in the sure to come feeding frenzy. And when they are done, it is expected that they will turn their eyes to other prey in Europe including the UK.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/05/african-resilience.php</link>
      <guid>0240c6bd531a4c2cde61b4d0e7d659c3</guid>
      <title>African Resilience</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It never ceases to amaze me when many people are amazed at the resilience of the African people. Considering the harsh environment especially in the recent times that Africans have to live through, think Zimbabwe, you have to be resilient and persistent to survive. Stories like &lt;a title="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/africa/8538587.stm" href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/africa/8538587.stm" target="_blank"&gt;BBC News - Zimbabwe's forgotten children, struggling to survive&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.nytimes.com/2010/04/11/opinion/11kristof.html?src=tp"&gt;Op-Ed Columnist - Young Superheroes in a Hut - NYTimes.com&lt;/a&gt; express surprise at this survival instinct.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/05/brazils-sexy-image.php</link>
      <guid>bea902c039f3329458c592a31f481c7e</guid>
      <title>Brazil's Sexy Image</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Someone told me in the recent past that Brazil and in particular Rio, wished to clean up their 'sexy' reputation as it gave foriegners the impression that Brazil is full of sex crazed people, especially the women. Not sure that President Lula'sreinforcement of theBrazil Health minister's call to have sex for better health (&lt;a href="http://en.mercopress.com/2010/04/29/more-sex-to-combat-high-blood-pressure-recommends-brazilian-minister" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.mercopress.com/2010/04/29/more-sex-to-combat-high-blood-pressure-recommends-brazilian-minister&lt;/a&gt;) will help that reputation much. Couple that with my earlier post '&lt;a title="Sexy Brazilian Males Need Help!" href="/blog/2010/04/sexy-brazilian-males-need-help.php"&gt;Sexy Brazilian Males Need Help!&lt;/a&gt;', this is a country where sex appears to be a national obsession.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/05/reading-and-driving-bus-driver-suspended-next-taxi-drivers.php</link>
      <guid>6a0982b6178bbdbf4246299b3acf71d1</guid>
      <title>Reading and Driving Bus Driver Suspended - Next Taxi Drivers</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A bus driver has been suspended after a passenger filmed him reading while driving.The West Midlands Travel driver steering with his elbows while holding a small boook. (&lt;a target="_blank" href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/england/west_midlands/8632920.stm"&gt;BBC News - Bus driver filmed reading while driving in Birmingham&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/05/mexicos-immigration-dilemma.php</link>
      <guid>8f10c0e1b7bf628c540b00563b89a498</guid>
      <title>Mexico&#x2019;s Immigration Dilemma</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Immigration, the world over, causes no end of unjustified hysteria and problems. Our politicians and newspapers in the UK love to take a swipe at immigrants every time they need someone to blame or just to give a good kick. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/05/africas-continued-dependence-on-europe.php</link>
      <guid>164ffe07b7a708c02c72f2a940f02390</guid>
      <title>Africa&#x2019;s Continued Dependence on Europe</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Brazilian president Luiz In&#xE1;cio Lula da Silva recently boasted that Brazil does the same amount of trade in Latin America and it does with the US and EU. (see &lt;a href="http://is.gd/bY48J" target="_blank"&gt;http://is.gd/bY48J&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/04/vote-clegg-get-brown.php</link>
      <guid>11596976ed75eeb7470aaf1801daea60</guid>
      <title>"Vote Clegg, get Brown."</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here is one of the reasons why 'elections' don't work for many people. When the leader of a party is urging voters to use tactical voting to elect them or to 'keep someone out of office' (&lt;a href="http://www.guardian.co.uk/commentisfree/2010/apr/20/labour-lib-dem-dilemma-rage" target="_blank"&gt;Here&#x2019;s what Labour can do about the Lib Dem dilemma&lt;/a&gt;), it would appear to me that my vote does not count for much in the grand scheme of things. What if I do like Clegg and genuinely want him to win, how do I do that without voting for him?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/04/natures-lessons.php</link>
      <guid>17521ee080c1ebfcbd61ec0c595fe0a3</guid>
      <title>Nature&#x2019;s lessons</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&#x201C;More than 1,000km from the event itself, Iceland&#x2019;s second volcanic eruption in the space of a month has caused flights in the UK to be grounded.&#x201D; &lt;a href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/sci/tech/8621992.stm" target="_blank"&gt;BBC News - Iceland volcano: Why a cloud of ash has grounded flights&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/04/the-rhodesian-mentality.php</link>
      <guid>138304aee82a9eaddd6935e47a92add6</guid>
      <title>The Rhodesian Mentality</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The stories over the past few days about the death of South Africa&#x2019;s defender of apartheid has had me shaking my head and today&#x2019;s story about his funeral and the reaction and comments of his followers gave me a sense of d&#xE9;j&#xE0;-vu (&lt;a href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/africa/8612017.stm" target="_blank"&gt;BBC News - Eugene Terreblanche: Love and hate&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/04/the-world-conspires-with-you.php</link>
      <guid>23e891d79dfa6b926c1ffc2918469ea9</guid>
      <title>The World Conspires With You</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you regularly read my blog, you will know that I tend to take anything sold by the &#x2018;quote a minute&#x2019; self help American gurus with a large pinch of salt. One of the central planks of the success brigade is that if you decide where you are going, the world will conspire to help you.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/04/tennis-girl-sadness.php</link>
      <guid>e948f062bd0f725446c5807735e3e0fb</guid>
      <title>&#x2018;Tennis Girl&#x2019; Sadness</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am not so sure why but this story from the BBC website made me sad. I think, but I am not sure, it has something to do with &#x2018;5 minutes of fame&#x2019; or is there a sense that there is much more to the story than meets the eye?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/03/negative-friends-and-yes-men.php</link>
      <guid>ecc77370ec7e73c202fffdc79bf14790</guid>
      <title>Negative Friends and Yes Men</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you happen to be one of the millions of people who either read or listen to the success self-help gurus that the USA seems to be able to generate in their thousands sprouting such terms as NLP, the Secret, 10 habits and other such like, the you would recognise the advice that you do not need to have negative friends.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/03/joy-is-like-sex.php</link>
      <guid>788f177fe1378183a18ee858ce8bfa58</guid>
      <title>Joy is like sex</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;"Money brings happiness. Fine. In that case, everyone who earns enough to have a high standard of living would be able to stop work. But then they&#x2019;re more troubled than ever, as if they were afraid of losing everything. Money attracts money, that&#x2019;s true. Poverty might bring unhappiness, but money wont necessarily bring happiness.I spent a lot of my life looking for happiness, now what I want is joy. Joy is like sex &#x2013; it begins and ends. I want pleasure. I want to be contended, but happiness? I no longer fall into that trap."&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/03/love-being-alone.php</link>
      <guid>524cf3be1f649d64290fb94a79ff61be</guid>
      <title>Love Being Alone</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&#x201C;If you cannot be by yourself for an hour, or for a day, or for a week then you don&#x2019;t like yourself&#x201D; so rants &#x2018;Payroll da Pimp&#x2019; in his &#x2018;Rebirth&#x2019; audio book. [WARNING : Do not look this book up if you are easily offended &#x2013; whilst the book is positive &#x2013; the language used to deliver it is likely to upset, if you are over, say, 30 .] Dr. Wayne Dyer, internationally best-selling author of &#x2018;The Power Of Intention&#x2019; is reported to have said &#x201C;You cannot be lonely if you like the person you're alone with.&#x201D;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2010 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/03/the-right-to-be-happy.php</link>
      <guid>f19240cac5eebb40ad2a13952c8e9dcc</guid>
      <title>The Right To Be Happy</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&#x201C;We hold these truths to be self-evident, that all men are created equal, that they are endowed by their Creator with certain unalienable Rights, that among these are Life, Liberty and the pursuit of Happiness.&#x201D;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/03/facebook-helps-you-get-syphilis.php</link>
      <guid>72531f2aa97904f5667bc7e5e06e84ca</guid>
      <title>Facebook Helps You Get Syphilis</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;But a facebook spokesman point out that "Facebook is no more responsible for STD transmission than newspapers are responsible for bad vision",   a snide poke at the silly newspaper stories pointing to a link between the use of the social networking sites such as Facebook and the spread of sexually transmitted disease syphilis, because such sites make it easier for people to meet new partners. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2010 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/03/school-asthma-death-due-to-negligence.php</link>
      <guid>40dcee03f16e94b77bc980bacfe6664f</guid>
      <title>School Asthma Death Due to Negligence</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Considering that it is a known fact that the incidents of asthma are increasing in the UK, the death of Sam Linton last week is a scary issue for those of us who have children who suffer from it. The fact that it wasdecided that it was due to neglect makes this such a sad incident.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2010 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/03/man-on-trial-over-airport-bomb-tweet.php</link>
      <guid>ee32b6a7e72eb3069b4dd6d3376d5e0b</guid>
      <title>Man on trial over airport bomb tweet</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Should we file this under "Waste of Taxpayers' Money"? Did Paul Chambers have the means to do so? Did he really mean it or it was said because the damn airport was closed? Doncaster has an airport? You learn something everyday.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/03/not-waiting-for-god.php</link>
      <guid>522ad0ce3691a7ce4a3b27329a83629a</guid>
      <title>I'm Not Waiting for God.</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You see them after travelling peak hours in the UK, every weekday, shuffling on the buses with their free passes, in some places trying to get on the bus before off peak time. You see them once or twice a week queued up outside post offices and if you happen into a pub (bar), they are there, nursing a pint of something for hours sometimes playing cards or dominos or choosing horses or greyhounds from some broadsheet newspaper and sending the 'bookie' runabout to place a bet for them. You might also spot them in the local butcher or at the Wednesday market buying two sausages for 'tea'. My wife will tell you that nothing frightens her husband more that joining the ranks of the 'one foot in the grave' brigade.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/03/pension-freeze-must-be-lifted.php</link>
      <guid>dce4c397a1e3ff2cd87d62af56b891c6</guid>
      <title>Pension freeze must be lifted.</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;"Pensioners who moved to countries such as Australia and Canada only receive the level of pension paid at retirement - which might be only &#xA3;6 per week. A court ruling from the European Court of Human Rights will decide on Tuesday whether they should receive increases."&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2010 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/03/malawi-police-chasing-gays.php</link>
      <guid>9ba8aa89c348861b0dbcfbb04aeb0524</guid>
      <title>Malawi: Police Chasing Gays</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;"Lilongwe &#x2014; Malawi is quickly becoming unsafe for homosexuals as the country's police service recently launched a campaign to hunt down and arrest prominent people who are suspected of being gay."&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/03/donors-mother-meets-saved-girl.php</link>
      <guid>a7f8f7785dba5da95047a7d440139372</guid>
      <title>Donor's Mother Meets Saved Girl</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For the first time in Scotland a family who donated their dead relatives organs and the person that received one of them have met. See &lt;a href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/scotland/glasgow_and_west/8555243.stm" target="_blank"&gt;BBC News - Mother meets girl who received sons liver&lt;/a&gt;. This story made me feel good about the fact that I have chosen and made known that I wish to be an organ donor after I 'kick the bucket'. If you have thought about it and not done anything about it, now is the time and do it now.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/03/the-haunting-of-my-heart.php</link>
      <guid>b72866c12252269d62f33ea062f6f936</guid>
      <title>The Haunting Of My Heart</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"As you move into your forties and fifties, the recognition of your own mortality becomes more and more a part of decision-making. You realize that you're not going to be around forever. Your choices become a lot more precious. The gap between your dreams and what you're actually doing narrows, and you start living your life more directly. What you're doing is who you are. And who you are becomes more important to you."&lt;/em&gt; See the full article this was taken from @ &lt;a href="http://www.fastcompany.com/magazine/13/hbrplus.html" target="_blank"&gt;Is Your Job Your Calling (extended interview) | Fast Company&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/03/pitbull-law-have-your-say.php</link>
      <guid>233219a4015a96bc1d535aa331237d3b</guid>
      <title>Pitbull Law - Have your say</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With the growing number of dog attacks in the past few years, many resulting in bad injuries and even death, the government launches a public consultation today on proposed changes to the current dangerous dogs laws. The measures include:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2010 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/03/is-teaching-the-last-choice-profession.php</link>
      <guid>17d20276eeefe8e7a955f7faba3e753f</guid>
      <title>Is teaching the last choice profession?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;According to a story on the BBC (&lt;a href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/education/8550506.stm" target="_blank"&gt;http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/education/8550506.stm&lt;/a&gt;), the number of men applying for teacher training has risen sharply because of the recession, says the body responsible for training teachers. There was a 52% rise in the number of men wanting to be primary school teachers - more than 4,700 in 2009/10, up about 1,500 compared with 2008/09.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2010 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/03/gain-without-pain.php</link>
      <guid>bb8da32a029fa693fef63add33f47906</guid>
      <title>Gain without Pain</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This morning, my son gave me one of those school photograph packs from school. You know the ones I mean? Where the schools get the photographer in and then encourage us, the gullible parents, to pay over the odds for the photographs? I do understand that school get a cut but I suspect the photographer doesn't do to badly out of it either. Of course, this prompted the question of justifying paying the exorbitant price with the boy vocalising his opinion that the photographs must be purchased. After all, these are &lt;em&gt;school&lt;/em&gt; photos.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2010 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/03/readers-will-pay-for-quality-journalism.php</link>
      <guid>d34ad5d1061e461366354716388764ab</guid>
      <title>Readers will pay for 'quality' journalism</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;"Publishers should have more balls, they should have more confidence about what they're doing," is how Rob Grimshaw, managing director of FT.com put it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/03/made-for-each-other.php</link>
      <guid>40e772220c51571d0af60fd047fdf17f</guid>
      <title>Made for each other</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A US couple has spent the first night of married life in separate prison cells after the bride attacked the grooms former lover after the wedding.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2010 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/03/whos-afraid-of-big-bad-death.php</link>
      <guid>bdc7b6afcd630c2e8b225daf2a904673</guid>
      <title>Who's afraid of big bad death?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I can't remember where I heard this little tit-bit but it is one I always recall it whenever I have to tell someone I am an atheist. In the story, a Muslim man asks a Christian man why is it he (the Christian) is afraid to die if he truly believes in heaven. It is obvious from countless survival stories we hear about, that many of us do everything we can to stay alive even to the point of suffering greatly. Is that fear of death?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2010 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/03/zimbabwe-indigenous-ownership-helpful.php</link>
      <guid>11b4089809304d6b35b5dcd1177499e1</guid>
      <title>Zimbabwe indigenous ownership - helpful?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A new Zimbabwean law that forces foreign-owned companies to sell a majority stake in their businesses to indigenous people has come into effect.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/02/happiness-not-so-good.php</link>
      <guid>22eb28af3971ceb69d16e0c4aaca7558</guid>
      <title>Happiness - Not so Good</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;"This latest finding adds to a wealth of data suggesting that being happy isn't all it's cracked up to be.... Happiness seems to make people more selfish, the latest in a series of revelations suggesting it changes how you think &#x2013; and not in a good way."&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2010 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/02/asylum-applications-fall.php</link>
      <guid>2477f57fac83420f58638c733f1d116f</guid>
      <title>Asylum Applications Fall But ....</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Asylum applications for the last three months of 2009 were the lowest since the early 1990's. Border and Immigration Minister Phil Woolas ia reported to have said" ...Our border has never been stronger, as shown by the fall in the number of asylum applications."&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/02/impersonal-business.php</link>
      <guid>aabc49772bca826d438b054a1b70c602</guid>
      <title>Impersonal Business</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How we in the West are accepting worsening 'customer care' under the pretence of efficiency.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/02/the-secret-of-contentment.php</link>
      <guid>d677a199de2f212fa264dc7483238617</guid>
      <title>The Secret Of Contentment...</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Those who face that which is actually before them, unburdened by the past, undistracted by the future, these are they who live, who make the best use of their lives; these are those who have found the secret of contentment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2010 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2010/01/where-to-from-here.php</link>
      <guid>2f64003146205e0bf35a4958f54aa2b2</guid>
      <title>Where to from here?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have finally called time on the last 10 years of my life. Somehow I knew it would come to this with the recent years' frustrations ensuring that to stay would not be possible. Can I say that I am disappointed? Well yes, I can because my expectations were, maybe unrealistically, much higher than the actual reality. Am I grateful? Yes I am. I am old and ugly enough to know that millions of people do not have the opportunity that presents itself to me now.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2010 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/12/when-did-i-stop-having-fun.php</link>
      <guid>327feb0296118b8d730fd1c70c6958b6</guid>
      <title>When Did I Stop Having Fun?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Most of the time I don't have much fun. The rest of the time I don't have any fun at all. - Woody Allen (1935 - )&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2009 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/12/someone-elses-dream.php</link>
      <guid>a47bc0f4a84d78fd36f8ad78b8830d35</guid>
      <title>Someone Else's Dream</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;"Never hold on hoping that you will benefit from someone else's dream - it inevitably means your dreams don't come true" Ben Ellis 2009&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/11/time-for-a-news-change.php</link>
      <guid>0852b32a9060a50e69593d3a57bce330</guid>
      <title>Time for A News Change.</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Many of us who have to work for a living have over the years got used to the idea that if the skills we brought to the market place were ever to become uneconomical, we would be redundant. We would need to re-train and gain new skills to continue with any sort of gainful employment. This is the part of our capitalist system and we, the workers, should understand this simple economic truth.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2009 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/11/integrity-is-it-still-important.php</link>
      <guid>2e0d107ebd4e87261a212b3136ed7fbb</guid>
      <title>Integrity - is it still important?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There have been a few stories over the last week or so about the scam advertisements on social sites mainly Facebook, arguably the most successful social site. It appears to have started with this commentary &#x2013; &lt;a href="http://www.techcrunch.com/2009/10/31/scamville-the-social-gaming-ecosystem-of-hell/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.techcrunch.com/2009/10/31/scamville-the-social-gaming-ecosystem-of-hell/&lt;/a&gt; on Techcrunch. One of the Facebook successful applications company&#x2019;s CEO can be seen discussing his early strategy in an online video where he basically said he did whatever was necessary to have a successful business &#x2013; see &lt;a href="http://feedproxy.google.com/%7Er/Techcrunch/%7E3/8R96Mx4zId8/" target="_blank"&gt;http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/8R96Mx4zId8/&lt;/a&gt;. Many of these companies are being held up as successful start-ups with multi-million valuations based on the number of users they appear to be attracting.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2009 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/10/more-calories-required.php</link>
      <guid>9058c1447d5434d4bb3f6b088c62b012</guid>
      <title>More Calories Required.</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am trying to get back in to my walk routine after my unintentional mini break and it has been a mixed bag. Wednesday was very slow and I did feel a bit woozy on the last lap but I persevered and completed. Yesterday, I felt so much better that my last lap was in the realms of my average lap speed.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2009 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/10/experts-and-vested-interests.php</link>
      <guid>577a595dd56c054ac3e07e9b7f76be28</guid>
      <title>Experts and Vested Interests</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It is quite amazing just how many people take expert advice at face value, even the Government does it. When I mention that I was walking as exercise, people look at me like I have lost it. And yet, walking is good exercise and a few keep fit sites do have articles on this form of exercise though usually aimed at the 'oldies'. The playing down of walking as exercise is very much about vested interests of the fitness industry, after all, who will pay to walk?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/10/in-the-autumn-of-our-lives.php</link>
      <guid>9c8333441043b36615b5d6366af4b6f6</guid>
      <title>In the autumn of our lives</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After a 12 day break from walking in the morning, I returned to experience the full colours of Autumn in the trees and on the grounds. I may not like the cold and wet but I do find the colours so much richer and I love it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2009 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/10/physician-heal-thyself-with-a-little-help.php</link>
      <guid>1a12bff621e8726ccb56db3813299b5d</guid>
      <title>Physician, Heal thyself&#x2026;with a little help</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Another way to break bad habits, dependencies and addictions is with a little help from your friends.  Whereas alcohol dependency is likely to be hidden, nicotine addiction is usually more open and people around you are more willing to accept its very addictive nature.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2009 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/10/walking-the-double-whammy.php</link>
      <guid>299053caee018c9bf5dc01ae0e8ec08a</guid>
      <title>Walking - the double Whammy</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have also up walking in the morning - except having missed 10 or so days now due to injured leg and the cold/flu. Walking replaced the gym with a few weeks of inactivity in the middle. The gym had to go on two counts, firstly I did not enjoy the experience and two, it was difficult to fit into my normal routine especially since the train companies decided to change their timetables at a very crucial time when I needed to create the habit.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2009 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/10/nobody-knows-my-fight.php</link>
      <guid>2db576f63569ad9e4d5e55f9c64465cf</guid>
      <title>Nobody Knows My Fight</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I just sort of naturally settled down to 4 to 6 drinks a day (night) and I usually have the higher number if I stay up later - now usually a Thursday night and a Sunday night which is when a number of TV programs I enjoy. The other nights I try to get to bed early enough to ensure I get enough sleep. This is a left-over from a previous healthy episode that I never quite let go off.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2009 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/10/kick-in-the-pants-too.php</link>
      <guid>9c0521a008d8819a25cdb88e510119cd</guid>
      <title>Kick in the Pants Too</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;During the following period, I have taken up exercising again, walking to work and on some days walking back, rewarding myself with a pint or two at the local pub when accomplished prior to arrival home. In the early part of the period, I tried to reinforce my talk and motivate myself on my morning walk to stay on the straight and narrow. I am still doing 8 to 10 cans of lager a day, the majority at home in the evening - but suffering so much less in the mornings! Most times, after the walk, nothing was felt at all!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2009 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/10/deja-vu-unconscious-warnings.php</link>
      <guid>bce96687e41fb080435597950760a69b</guid>
      <title>D&#xE9;j&#xE0; vu - Unconscious warnings?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;"Several psychoanalysts attribute d&#xE9;j&#xE0; vu to simple fantasy or wish fulfillment, while some psychiatrists ascribe it to a mismatching in the brain that causes the brain to mistake the present for the past. Many parapsychologists believe it is related to a past-life experience. Obviously, there is more investigation to be done." (&lt;a href="http://www.howstuffworks.com/question657.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.howstuffworks.com/question657.htm&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2009 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/10/feeling-hedged-in-dream.php</link>
      <guid>ff291b96c8d34f4889be365e55fd85fe</guid>
      <title>Feeling Hedged In - Dream</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I rarely remember dreams but when I do, they do tend to memorable. Had one just the other day and wondered if it had anything to do with the fact that I feel a bit restricted, hemmed in, if you like, even though it was not stifling, if you know what I mean.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2009 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/09/curvy-workmates-are-even-better.php</link>
      <guid>9ae1224e804610b11af02ed0e8409d1e</guid>
      <title>Curvy Workmates are even better!</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;'Storm in a tea cup' rubbish.  Why do some women want all men, especially educated ones, to be dead from the waist down?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2009 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/09/identity-stolen-day-4.php</link>
      <guid>286fb07f6affbc910585d870b79eec0c</guid>
      <title>Identity Stolen: Day 4</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;All the excitement has died down, there does not appear much I can do else.  I phoned police to update details and to tell them I knew who had actually done this.  After a pleasant and fairly detailed conversation, it is very obvious that it will requires the banks or finance companies to ask the police to get involved if it is to go any further.    This is because in most cases, they are regarded as the victim of the crime not you who has had your identity stolen.  The policeman did also mention that because the sum of money was not really a lot (to a bank), chances where the matter would not be taken on, I have a feeling that my id thief knew this too.  I suppose the banks' lawyers don't get out of bed for less that &amp;#163;5K!  Impersonating a police office is a crime, impersonating another citizen does not appear to be so.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2009 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/09/identity-stolen-day-3.php</link>
      <guid>f234bc5ead9598a6326f1c490cb3a9bd</guid>
      <title>Identity Stolen: Day 3</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Decided to ring the police first thing in the morning, to update the report with the extra information I had but ended holding on for so long that I gave up.  Just as I was leaving the house for work, my security code from checkmyfile came in the post.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2009 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/09/identity-stolen-day-2.php</link>
      <guid>4295fb04bdb4784edb4df627050d81fc</guid>
      <title>Identity Stolen: Day 2</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After my unsuccessful evening, I waited until just after nine to contact the relevant people.  Started by emailing checkmyfile.co.uk to find out if there is an alternative way to obtain my credit reports sooner than the three days, I was informed it would take.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2009 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/09/identity-stolen-day-1.php</link>
      <guid>1afd348384882583dbab9d89dad7c571</guid>
      <title>Identity Stolen: Day 1</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Thursday started like normal until about lunchtime, I got a phone call at work, on the work landline number, from a company called paydayloansuk.co.uk.  The ensuring conversation which was supposed to be about my recent application was no doubt confusing both for the caller and myself with me refusing to answer any 'security' questions and her refusing to release any details of my application.  The conversation ended with a promise to send me a text message about the issue, no mobile phone number asked for or given.  Said text message was not received and I put it down to a possible dubious sales tactic.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2009 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/08/fatpeoplearesexier-trending-on-twitter.php</link>
      <guid>40ed60566fab277cbc1e621a7487072a</guid>
      <title>#fatpeoplearesexier Trending on Twitter</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;And just to re-inforce my earlier article &lt;a href="slob-is-the-new-sex-god.php"&gt;Slob is The New Sex God'&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/search?q=%23fatpeoplearesexier" target="_blank"&gt;#fatpeoplearesexier&lt;/a&gt; is trending today on twitter.  Apparently started by &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/shanedawsontv" target="_blank"&gt;Shane Dawson&lt;/a&gt;, a minor youtube sensation.  Someone left a comment saying he was a bad influence because of his obesity so he made a vlog saying how much he loves fat people.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2009 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/08/2mp-camera-good-enough-for-flickr.php</link>
      <guid>15a2cb214c7868ecfc4b6c6dec560f25</guid>
      <title>2mp Camera good enough for flickr?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://mashable.com/2009/08/17/iphone-flickr/" target="_blank"&gt;http://mashable.com/2009/08/17/iphone-flickr/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apparently the iPhone is being used heavily for taking and uploading photos onto Flickr.  It will be interesting to see if Flickr remains the top photo site especially for the professionals with this reduction in the quality of photographs.  I suspect the explosion will continue at least for a while and it will be harder to find photographs on the service.&lt;br /&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/08/boxed-in.php</link>
      <guid>13fd2ecc835d9b404160ddf793b1d6f5</guid>
      <title>Boxed In?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The has reported that most people feel like the new houses in the UK are too small making modern living quite difficult.  Apparently the floor area and room sizes are the smallest in Europe but should we be surprised?  After all, the accomodation that factory owners built for their workers during the Industrial Revolution makes even the efforts made by mining companies in Africa for their staff look fantastic.  Can't say the older houses are much better, can you?  Everywhere I have lived has always felt a bit cramped.  More details at &lt;a href="http://www.cabe.org.uk/news/new-homes-are-too-small-for-everyday-life"&gt;http://www.cabe.org.uk/news/new-homes-are-too-small-for-everyday-life&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2009 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/08/slob-is-the-new-sex-god.php</link>
      <guid>f830f28ebf4063fdc40b000fe83c4ed2</guid>
      <title>Slob is the New Sex God</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;"But it's daft to suggest that everyone previously thought most women were turned on by men with fastidiously toned bodies, reeking of cologne, hair made Himalayan with 'product', dressed in gleaming Hugo Boss and generally showing every sign of effortful, self-absorbed vanity." &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2009 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/08/when-i-was-a-child-women-over-50-ran-the-world.php</link>
      <guid>a89ab0fc79dc24ad096d827ae3d39b36</guid>
      <title>When I was a child, women over 50 ran the world</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;"At 50 plus ... I never imagined I'd still be parting with money at makeup counters, or that I'd be racing off for a blow-dry when threatened with a photographer. I assumed I'd wear my hair in round perm, the colour of steel and as tough. Think of the time I'd save; vanity is such a consumer of the hours."&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2009 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/08/iphone-happiness.php</link>
      <guid>0c082f4210fcb502a93c40d4ee8f7a97</guid>
      <title>iPhone Happiness</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Even the staid old scientists are getting into this popular culture thingy. You can now take part in a scientific study of happiness with your iPhone - &lt;a href="https://www.trackyourhappiness.org/" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.trackyourhappiness.org/&lt;/a&gt;.  Since this blog is about that very thing, I'm going to have a go, so watch this space, I may be the happiest person on the planet, NOT!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2009 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/07/coincidence-or-awareness.php</link>
      <guid>abda42062a02a1786ba7f7a35548155f</guid>
      <title>Coincidence or Awareness?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On the train to work yesterday morning I noticed graffiti stating simply 'Zulu 1875'. Intrigued, a Google search later at work revealed a lot of Zulu references to the period around 1875. Notably though, the Anglo Zulu war is officially regarded as being during 1879, some 6 years after Cetshwayo became Zulu King, maybe sub consciously I knew something was not right about the date, who knows? Today, I received a newsletter from O'Reilly Media in which a quick browse revealed that recently, Tim O'Reilly, the CEO of O'Reilly Media, had written a blog post entitled '&lt;a href="http://post.oreilly.com/rd/9z1zmd8pp1h12sauqvudn5ojo5llo0fsjgi4qqj9658" target="_blank"&gt;Seeing Our Culture with Fresh Eyes&lt;/a&gt;' about a book he had recently read about Zulu uprising in South Africa around that time. Mr O'Reilly, by the way, is a man I respect and admire to the point of following on Twitter, as the man who runs the company that I should.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2009 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/07/not-the-way-to-die.php</link>
      <guid>8dc713d63d5f3646f88fbdc9520c4fea</guid>
      <title>Not the way to die</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;"The body of pensioner has been found in a tenement flat in Edinburgh where it may have lain for up to five years"&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2009 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/06/company-short-term-memory-loss.php</link>
      <guid>2ce447c40ebb167e1bfed62773af2992</guid>
      <title>Company Short Term Memory Loss?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In a crisis, can you call on your workers to tighten their belts with you to save the company?  Many businesses may feel that they can but you have to question how enthusiastically those same workers will be.  Will they have forgotten previous company behaviour towards them? ( &lt;a href="/blog/2008/11/if-you-say-nice-things-will-they-promote-you.php"&gt;If you say nice things, will they promote you?&lt;/a&gt; )  BA seems to hope so despite asking their employees to take unpaid time-off or to work for no pay (yeah right!).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2009 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/06/is-bankster-to-be-the-millionth-english-word.php</link>
      <guid>2d4f5830726cd7a1c08e7b14e397a9d6</guid>
      <title>Is 'bankster' to be the millionth English Word?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;'Bankster'  - a cross between a banker and a gangster  - has the chance of being the English's millionth word.  Honestly though, I thought the words where inter-changeable considering the many years that banks have been skinning the public and the bloody mess they've put us in with their financial carelessness 8-).  &lt;a href="http://www.guardian.co.uk/books/2009/jun/10/english-million-word-milestone" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.guardian.co.uk/books/2009/jun/10/english-million-word-milestone&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2009 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/05/facebook-suffers-from-big-business-arrogance.php</link>
      <guid>b5013981ddee365d2e14e02d7f461eb6</guid>
      <title>Facebook suffers from 'big business' arrogance</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Apparently Facebook have had the cheek to move some Welsh cities and towns into England.  The cheek of it!  see &lt;a href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/wales/8052252.stm" target="_blank"&gt;http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/wales/8052252.stm&lt;/a&gt;.  I groaned when I read 'Some users e-mailed the US-based site since Friday to alert it to the error.' What email address did they use?  I spent over an hour on Facebook trying and failing to discover an email address to inform them that one of their 'recommended' friend suggestions was a person who has sadly passed away. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/05/boffins-dont-have-all-answers.php</link>
      <guid>e9f543d6421ab0f98a89bcad500b4072</guid>
      <title>Boffins don't have all answers</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It is amazing how many people take scientists as the unquestionable experts.  Some of us know that some times there are vested interests where scientists are 'pushed' towards certain conclusions, usually to attract funding.  You also have the ones that seem to research the bleeding obvious and those that seem to serve no useful purpose but to keep the boffins busy.  Make up your mind on &lt;a href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/earth/hi/earth_news/newsid_8050000/8050298.stm" target="_blank"&gt;this story&lt;/a&gt; but it does prove many answers still elude us.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2009 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/05/the-meaning-of-karma.php</link>
      <guid>f0855fba0a813e6dc56be092d5ef4b14</guid>
      <title>The meaning of karma</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I tend to use the word karma to describe the calm, peaceful balance. Something that disturbs this state is said to be upsetting my karma. I recently decided to look it up the proper meaning of the word and am horrified to discover that it doesn't mean anything like that at all. I am not sure where my interpretation of it came and that got me to thinking as to how best to describe this search.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2009 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/04/time-to-complain.php</link>
      <guid>26e8bb053f5b390745972b592de33944</guid>
      <title>Time to Complain?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Who are these people that find time to complain about adverts?  Good to see the Advertising Standards Authority do seem to have a mind of their own.  See the list at &lt;a href="http://www.guardian.co.uk/media/organgrinder/2009/apr/29/asa-most-complained-about-adverts-2008" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.guardian.co.uk/media/organgrinder/2009/apr/29/asa-most-complained-about-adverts-2008&lt;/a&gt;.  Of the ones shown here, the Barnado's advert was the one I did not like.  Frankly I found it disturbing because of the scene repetition - I suppose that was intentional.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2009 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/04/time-is-more-important-than-money.php</link>
      <guid>a208306c3dfff64679a9341307835de4</guid>
      <title>Time is more important than money.</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is typical me. I can't believe it been over a month since I wrote in this blog, totally unacceptable! The release of the 1911 Census data took me back to a project I started over 3 years ago and overtaken by events. And as usual I have become obsessed again to the detriment of other things.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2009 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/02/zimbabwes-rock-bottom.php</link>
      <guid>ad34e529613354b0a96be4970664aa1d</guid>
      <title>Zimbabwe's Rock Bottom?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;"Since my last report he has reached rock bottom, and has started to dig" or in other words, an old saying involving a frying pan and fire.  I just got forwarded this old email chain letter about 'army insults' and guess what came to mind?  Zimbabwe.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2009 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/02/under-the-weather.php</link>
      <guid>aa956a76836063c5e1063d1ba6eb88fa</guid>
      <title>Under the weather?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Saturday was my birthday and I didn't do much in the way of celebrations, in fact I didn't really feel in a celebratory mood. For some reason I woke up with the image of a blue sky, my children laughing and splashing in a clear blue sea, a white sandy beach with lovely big picnic spread and the smell of fish and meat on the barbeque. Everything I did just did not seem to shake that picture from my head.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2009 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/02/lessons-learnt-i-dont-think-so.php</link>
      <guid>545dff600751240dd5668275cfd080b3</guid>
      <title>Lessons learnt?  I don't think so.</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;"....High street banks and building societies are cracking down on new lending to previously credit-worthy customers using an early warning system, which assesses the chances of borrowers defaulting on loan repayments in the future...."&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2009 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/02/twas-greed-that-got-us-thus-far.php</link>
      <guid>98f7373f8dd78752c7701dc8bdcd7127</guid>
      <title>T'was greed that got us thus far...</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here is a question.  Imagine that you are legally entitled to a &amp;#163;1 million bonus for one whole year of hard slog and stress, but however, everyone says or thinks you should not take the money as the company that you work for has not made any money.  In fact, had it not been the help of those who can only dream of that kind of money, it is lucky that you still have a job.  Would you take the money?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2009 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/02/no-child-maintenance-without-dna-testing.php</link>
      <guid>3685f5ca0940b973e3461f067fb06c12</guid>
      <title>No child maintenance without DNA testing!</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There is nothing in the UK to set off the gender war like the issue of Child Maintenance.  The welfare reform bill blog entry at &lt;a href="http://www.guardian.co.uk/commentisfree/2009/jan/27/child-support-absent-fathers-passport" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.guardian.co.uk/commentisfree/2009/jan/27/child-support-absent-fathers-passport&lt;/a&gt; is a good example of the feelings generated - getting nearly a thousand comments in a few days.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2009 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/02/theres-snow-news-like-snow-news.php</link>
      <guid>82b5b9eaae33d128ae773d86a548a718</guid>
      <title>There's Snow News Like Snow News</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I can't even be bothered to provide links to any snow stories; every single UK new source is carrying it.  I won't even go into how a Northern European country fails year after year to be prepared for a bit of snow.  This weather is like manna from heaven for the news gathers of our society as they are scratching the bottom of the barrel to give us any descent local news.  Don't believe me?  Well another thing I learnt from the news today is that following on from Blue Monday (see &lt;a href="/blog/2009/01/blue-monday-blues.php"&gt;Blue Monday Blues&lt;/a&gt; ), that the first Monday in February has been dubbed National Sickie Day and is statistically the worst day for absenteeism in the UK (see &lt;a href="http://thescotsman.scotsman.com/uk/It39s-unhappy-Monday-and-economic.4935004.jp" target="_blank"&gt;http://thescotsman.scotsman.com/uk/It39s-unhappy-Monday-and-economic.4935004.jp)&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2009 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/01/charity-does-do-good-for-you.php</link>
      <guid>bbf4ba976d2736aa0f3d9c35ad3f3bd8</guid>
      <title>Charity Does Do Good... For You.</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"How I invest and spend may touch the lives of people in distant places, whose names I'll never know, whose hopes I never think about"&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/business/7831002.stm" target="_blank"&gt;Attributed to Mr Shaunaka Rishi Das of the Oxford Centre for Hindu Studies.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2009 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/01/stop-press-aid-arrives-in-england.php</link>
      <guid>b7c12b5f2f2aaa19c89a5bde9c182c39</guid>
      <title>Stop Press: Aid arrives in England.</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;People in Iceland - a country currently in desperate economic trouble - have shipped jumpers and blankets to England this week.  A container of woolies arrived in the north-east of England after an appeal on an Icelandic radio station. They were handed to local charities in Hull on Thursday. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2009 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/01/is-ing-spinning-to-their-savers.php</link>
      <guid>ab673ddf7b0d4db340127139d3306740</guid>
      <title>Is ING SpinnING to their savers?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have savings with ING Direct and they keep trying to re-assure us savers that 'Your money is safe with ING Direct' and that it is part of one of the 20 largest financial institutions worldwide global financial company providing banking, investments, life insurance and retirement services with over &amp;#163;1 trillion in assets and yet....&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2009 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/01/police-taking-the-goat.php</link>
      <guid>1f002d61cf282a6c05c5ae619c045683</guid>
      <title>Police Taking the Goat</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Only in Africa can this sort of thing happen.  I laughed tears.  See it here &lt;a href="http://news.bbcn.co.uk/1/hi/world/africa/7846822.stm"&gt;Nigeria police hold 'robber' goat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2009 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/01/be-prepared.php</link>
      <guid>e7c50c21af95f205596f2a6c349c74a8</guid>
      <title>Be Prepared</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Scenario: It is 2015, the world is recovering from one of the last great recession but Europe and the USA are not doing so well. So many people were laid off in those years and countries led by China and Asia but including African and South American countries picked up the slack and now lead the world economy. Large European and American multi-nationals, many of which have been run and owned by foreign management and finance for many years, took advantage of the down turn to shift operation to 'cheaper' regions. The banks, the ones that were the main cause of the financial crisis, now de-nationalised by returning only a percentage of the billions of tax payers' money, are under pressure to return to the pre-recession profitability, are pressurizing the now the millions of now unemployed tax payers to make good on their mortgages and loans.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2009 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/01/obamas-biggest-burden.php</link>
      <guid>483c2140380789fa575ce9ced51ad75a</guid>
      <title>Obama's biggest burden.</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Well, finally it is done.  A non-white person now lives in the white house and expectations run very high.  That is unfortunate for Obama because there is bound to be some big disappointments along the way.  It's from these expectations that Obama's biggest task comes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2009 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/01/spirituality-and-being-an-atheist.php</link>
      <guid>89a00369757748f19e959948c4558d37</guid>
      <title>Spirituality and being an atheist.</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"Spirituality, in a narrow sense, concerns itself with matters of the spirit, a concept closely tied to religious belief and faith, a transcendent reality, or one or more deities. Spiritual matters are thus those matters regarding humankind's ultimate nature and meaning, not only as material biological organisms, but as beings with a unique relationship to that which is perceived to be beyond the bodily senses, time and the material world."&lt;/em&gt; [&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spirituality"&gt;Wikipaedia&lt;/a&gt;]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/01/blue-monday-blues.php</link>
      <guid>51d0a87aa376616c196c5c6efa4afe18</guid>
      <title>Blue Monday Blues</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The 5th of January I wrote and said things where going back to normal. How I lied! If anything Christmas time is the worst time for making you break habits you have tried to hard to maintain. The few days of not following routines are fatal to anything that requires a bit of effort on your part.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2009 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2009/01/happy-new-year-resolutions.php</link>
      <guid>9a8639d9e7a7b7f619de70062374a824</guid>
      <title>Happy New Year Resolutions!</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Well this is it, 2009 before we could even catch our breaths, everything's back to normal.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2009 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/12/another-blow-for-the-small-man.php</link>
      <guid>b7d76db082a083a7e59e553175804f53</guid>
      <title>Another Blow for the Small Man</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Or woman in this case.  I just love it when big corporate enterprises are brought to attention by a person working with resolve and right.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2008 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/12/understatement-of-the-year.php</link>
      <guid>dc4b7aba8a7d1000fcf01486af368c96</guid>
      <title>Understatement of the Year?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;"This is a landlocked country. And its formal and informal economies would suffer. Within a week, it would bring the economy on its knees," a senior US official said in Washington on condition of anonymity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2008 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/12/there-snow-news.php</link>
      <guid>1685f64bc9d03799cd3131f96daca255</guid>
      <title>There Snow News</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Boing! Boing! Boing!  Hello, here is the something o'clock news.  England has come to a stand-still again due to the half inch of snow that has fallen in the last 24 hours!  &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2008 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/12/there-is-a-god.php</link>
      <guid>d58ce7cf92a48deaf67f82ce726c8589</guid>
      <title>There is a God</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;"Only one group is more miserable than the retailers: the bankers and investment bankers."&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2008 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/11/these-teenagers-will-take-care-of-business.php</link>
      <guid>bb93955007a300cd3c9d3255630e2063</guid>
      <title>These teenagers will take care of business...</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;"Teenagers 'optimistic about jobs', 90% felt they would find work and more than half rejected the idea of signing on." (&lt;a href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/uk/7737720.stm" target="_blank"&gt;Teenagers 'optimistic about jobs'&lt;/a&gt;). Well we have been telling them for years to 'fulfill your destiny', 'stand up for yourself' and 'you can do it', should we be surprised?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2008 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/11/kenyan-gravy-train-gathers-speed.php</link>
      <guid>e754ac36144543a072acfd0b561445aa</guid>
      <title>Kenyan Gravy Train Gathers Speed</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Africa has gained a reputation over the years of corruption and many Western countries have made big noises especially when discussing aid.   So well versed are these arguments that you hear normal 'on the street' Joes using that as a reason 'not to give aid to African countries'.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2008 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/11/surprise-surprise-noses-in-the-trough-then.php</link>
      <guid>ffbf23cc703e8d249b7ef0f2266014a8</guid>
      <title>Surprise Surprise - noses in the trough then...</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Well, you could have knocked me over sideways - The administrators of the UK and European arm of bankrupt investment bank Lehman Brothers are making better money than the bankers. [See &lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/finance/newsbysector/banksandfinance/3460876/Lehmans-administrators-paid-more-than-the-bankers.html" target="_blank"&gt;Lehman's administrators paid more than the bankers&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2008 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/11/as-good-as-it-gets.php</link>
      <guid>fe43065a147b1a7c14fb3c255f87a928</guid>
      <title>As good as it gets?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In Zimbabwe, Arthur Mutambara, head of an MDC breakaway party which is also involved in the agreement, said the offer was "as good as it gets".  Arthur needs a reality check!  News story here - &lt;a href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/africa/7718989.stm" target="_blank"&gt;MDC rejects Zimbabwe cabinet plan&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2008 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/11/the-lowest-common-denominator.php</link>
      <guid>c5d82d31730d22c21f0969767ca2e4a5</guid>
      <title>The lowest common denominator</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I came across this blog entry &lt;a href="http://thecanadianrepublic.blogspot.com/2008/11/reason-obamaism-wont-last.html" target="_blank"&gt;The Reason Obamaism Won't Last&lt;/a&gt; - in the middle of the euphoria of Obama's election as the president of the USA. Whilst I have my own reservations about the elation of this momentous occasion, I still recognised the significance of this election.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2008 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/11/palin-probably-the-first-female-us-president.php</link>
      <guid>b3519d7e037c6a5bc646b23da5f36e26</guid>
      <title>Palin - Probably the first female US President.</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Well strike me sideways, I personally thought Obama would not do it,  Privately I thought this would be  high turn-out at the last minute - of the people that the pollsters will not have expected to vote - to ensure he did not win.  So far he is only 4% ahead in the popular vote but the job has been done.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2008 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/11/our-banks-keep-all-the-money.php</link>
      <guid>16b79538e6562542e5e6ffcfbb599d75</guid>
      <title>Our banks keep all the money</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Not only have we thrown billions at them to save them from their own greed, we now have to ask the greedy so and sos to pass interest rates back to us. Is something wrong here?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2008 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/11/does-passion-require-control.php</link>
      <guid>4fc3e7affa3edfc0ef77b760501a6013</guid>
      <title>Does passion require control?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Many years ago, my wife considered herself a computer widow. At the time, 'computing' was my hobby - more like a burning passion, but that's a matter of opinion! Computing is such a wide area but to those around me, I was obsessed with computers. As I was not in a position, at the time, to afford the best computers, I had to make do with what I had - so I built PCs, patched them and upgraded them for others in order to build a decent enough PC from the leftovers to do the things I wanted to. Many of the tools, the free/shareware ones obviously, were not always what I wanted so I programmedas well.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2008 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/10/first-obama-then-the-lord-of-the-pets.php</link>
      <guid>b15adf8b07496e8e4f48c8b80b24ff91</guid>
      <title>First Obama, then the Lord of The Pets...</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A *smile* news story where a British expat, Mark Lewis, who only speaks broken Spanish has become a mayor of a Spanish Town.  Councillor Lewis' previous/current post is that of 'Councillor for Animals' (heh?). Who says multi-culturalism doesn't work?  The story is at &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/europe/7701551.stm"&gt;Briton denies Spanish mayor role&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2008 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/10/patience-a-disappearing-virtue.php</link>
      <guid>84870d8bf94753a52406509d11f7c9b1</guid>
      <title>Patience - a disappearing virtue?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ahem. Went to the gym this evening and must say I struggled to be motivated to get there and to stay there once I got there. Put myself under some pressure to make the effort today since I had not been since Saturday and when I weighed myself this morning, I found I have actually put on weight. This on top of the weight I had put on the last time I checked, not really that bl***dy motivating, is it? I know, I know some people will have me believe that muscle weights more than fat but believe you me, I see no blasted muscle anywhere.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2008 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/10/it-is-only-democracy-when-i-say-so.php</link>
      <guid>d162ef83045325c3945597c3b2f0ad88</guid>
      <title>It is only democracy when I say so...</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;"Their behaviour is disgraceful and has no place in a modern democracy." so says Stockport's Councillor Dave Goddard about Stagecoaches' refusal  to carry Stockport council-funded adverts entitled "C-charge. Want to Pay? Have your say" on routes between Stockport and Manchester city centre.   Stagecoaches' response is that they support the introduction of the congestion charge and are actually using their own buses to carry their message. See the full story at &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/england/manchester/7696425.stm"&gt;Anger over C-charge bus adverts&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2008 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/10/usa-elections-not-exciting.php</link>
      <guid>df86db6bc2f2929526361f886fb6840d</guid>
      <title>USA Elections - not exciting</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You might be wondering why this watchful eye on Zimbabwe and none on the USA.  Not quite sure why but the USA elections has not gripped my imagination at all even when it appears  it will make history - well at least USA history.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2008 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/10/and-the-zimbabwean-prom-continues.php</link>
      <guid>8728b8364a9fe9523384cebe2d9bb4d6</guid>
      <title>And the Zimbabwean Prom continues....</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/africa/7680964.stm"&gt;Zimbabwe talks delayed for a week&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/10/inspiration-and-motivation.php</link>
      <guid>51f04eadb03d35b46b14384b3c6ab660</guid>
      <title>Inspiration and motivation.</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Well I did suspect that this stuff would not be easy. After all I am a man of habit and when I need to change any one of them, it takes a great deal of effort. In fact most change is forced upon you and usually with a lot of resistance.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2008 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/10/the-zimbabwe-saga-continues.php</link>
      <guid>537341ff5794602f9b41b8a290c952c6</guid>
      <title>The Zimbabwe saga continues</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Fom here &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/africa/7666493.stm"&gt;Mbeki seeks to save Zimbabwe deal&lt;/a&gt; to here &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/africa/7681468.stm"&gt;MDC seeks new Zimbabwe election&lt;/a&gt; and I am hating to say I told you so.  This is like a Xmas pantomime with the giant Bob not willing to wait for hesitant, indecisive Tsva as he needs to take control of the Kingdom.   A playground without leadership for too long time could go to the ---- (insert appropriate enemy here)! Especially since Tsva has been swaggering around feeling important just because he had the support of the playground next door's main man - who incidentally has found out that in his playground you could find yourself locked out with you closest associates running for the hole in the fence!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2008 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/10/mykey-teenage-remote-control.php</link>
      <guid>e7d099a8c0ce83720394addc798a8f68</guid>
      <title>MyKey - Teenage Remote Control</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ford Motor Company is introducing an innovative new technology - called MyKey - designed to help parents encourage their teenagers to drive safer, use fuel more efficiently and increase safety-belt usage.  How about another key for the idiot parents?  In fact since the maximum limit in this country is 70mph, how about not selling cars that do anything faster than that ( written whilst ducking from the drivel that will pour from every motorist's mouth )&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2008 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/10/sometimes-you-have-to-stand-up.php</link>
      <guid>b88443a010cee9f02122e2842cc30aa6</guid>
      <title>Sometimes you have to stand up ...</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;....and be counted.  Doesn't it make you feel good when someone stands up against wrong and forces some action?  It is especially satisfying when it is standing up to the 'authorities' who keep trying to tell us what to do and how to live.  You go, guy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2008 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/10/free-alcohol-where.php</link>
      <guid>4b572e22a12331e63de9ca12d6c793d3</guid>
      <title>Free alcohol? Where?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Apparently there are some bars offering free drinks to women.  Where?  Not in Birmingham or Wolverhampton.  We, Midlanders, including the female of the species, know how to wet our throats and so the local watering holes do not need to make desperate attempts to get us into their establishments :)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2008 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/10/where-does-1-today-230m-tomorrow.php</link>
      <guid>a4d283a5c3a532e18b504443436a1a18</guid>
      <title>Where does &amp;#163;1 today = &amp;#163;230m tomorrow?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Zimbabwe can't keep out of the news, can it?  See &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/africa/7660569.stm"&gt;Zimbabwe inflation hits new high&lt;/a&gt;.  I tried explaining to my nine and thirteen year old what 231,000,000% inflation means in real life.  Here is where I started.  If you have &amp;#163;230 million today, in a year it will buy the same items you can buy with today with $1!  Not that didn't work - so I tried the other option.  A sweet that costs &amp;#163;1 today will cost &amp;#163;230 million in a year's time.  Now I may not be entirely correct, but you can cut it whichever you want - there is a description for the situation that you would want to say to anyone under the age of 21!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2008 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/10/living-liverpool.php</link>
      <guid>fbb9748e2fc9803bedfb213e4c854506</guid>
      <title>Living Liverpool</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Have failed to look after the physical this week, with the conference in the middle of the week and I have been away for the weekend. For some crazy reason, I chose to go to Liverpool for a weekend break. It was a gamble and I was not sure the wife would approve and we both have been pleasantly surprised. Liverpool, like Birmingham, have had a bad rap. Maybe they deserved the reputation years ago &#x2013; I remember arriving in Birmingham some 18 years ago. It wasn&#x2019;t impressive then but it is very pleasant now as is Liverpool.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2008 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/10/why-care-about-ms.php</link>
      <guid>f08eb4a75e338feabcf120277c5e7a31</guid>
      <title>Why care about M&amp;amp;S?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Not sure if I picked this up from somewhere or whether I made it up myself, but for sometime I have been saying that 'you can tell the level of comfort in a society by the headlines of its independent press'.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2008 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/10/east-midlands-airport-why.php</link>
      <guid>a8719ec95b1578277d5fe6adaacfa90e</guid>
      <title>East Midlands Airport - why?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am really struggling to get into the daily upkeep of this blog. Additionally sometimes I just want to write about something that has no real relevance to self improvement and the four states of the human experience. But when I do, I will try to relate it because if I have to mention it, it must have had an effect. Well here goes for the next installment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2008 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/09/the-nothing-deal-zimbabwes-plight.php</link>
      <guid>fb5ea8d2403230d6bd87291899d3b490</guid>
      <title>The Nothing Deal - Zimbabwe's Plight</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Read the latest in this sad saga here - &lt;a href="#"&gt;NO LONGER AVAILABLE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/09/the-self-stocktake.php</link>
      <guid>88a87a808e4d8af9d600426c2ede85f6</guid>
      <title>The Self Stocktake</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Well, occasionally one has to stop and check the results of one&#x2019;s endeavours. It is the way we measure our successes and failures and I do not think there is a person on this planet that at some occasion has had to re-assess the position one is in. All successful businesses, big or small, do it on a regular basis!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2008 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/09/from-this-moment-on.php</link>
      <guid>c0c786b18efe5232a23426fb3451590b</guid>
      <title>From this moment on...</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;(With apologies to &lt;em&gt;LeAnn Rimes&lt;/em&gt;.)  All the changes I referred to in the last post,  I realise,  have led to something better though it may have not felt like it at the time.  To para-phase another country artist, Garth, &#x201C;.......... I could have missed the pain but I'd of had to miss the dance......&#x201D;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2008 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/09/its-been-change-all-the-way.php</link>
      <guid>0ceec9b92e7648d2e4e6d8c4dfa867c8</guid>
      <title>It's been change all the way</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Well today I suspect is the start of another round of changes.  I mean its only been a month or so when another two or maybe even three marriages of close people appear to heading for the rocks (see previous post).  And we have only just moved into this house a few months ago after 12 years in the same house where if I remember  correctly less than a year previously, the company I worked for was taken over and we moved offices miles away.  Screwed up my fitness schedule that did, as I  had to catch a bus and train instead of walk to work since then.  If I remember rightly, I started the new fitness regime after I discovered I was actually obese and not the sexy dude I thought I was.  I now have joined a gym to get rid of the new fat, another change to my well planned routine!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2008 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/09/where-are-the-balls.php</link>
      <guid>df80cb81fad01b99d9381defda8c0536</guid>
      <title>Where are the balls?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On the BBC news Site &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/business/7630578.stm"&gt;Bail-out fears return to markets&lt;/a&gt;.  The markets are apparently rising on bail-out hopes.  Now just wait a minute, I though the whole idea of business was to take a risk and therefore have the potential to make more money than if you left you money in some safe bank account  (not that banks are living up to that reputation currently).  Now it appears you can have gravy as well have the government bail you out when it all goes pear-shaped.  Something is wrong and smells very fishy (with apologies to the fish among you). &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2008 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/09/the-royal-society-of-sheep.php</link>
      <guid>b5d5b1d91b44eca1808f66fa642383a9</guid>
      <title>The Royal Society of Sheep?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Applaud Lord Robert Winston, professor of science and society at Imperial College London when he said: "I fear that in this action the Royal Society may have only diminished itself. This is not a good day for the reputation of science or scientists. This individual was arguing that we should engage with and address public misconceptions about science - something that the Royal Society should applaud." &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2008 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/09/the-new-mad-season.php</link>
      <guid>ea49623a32284fbf1a934b13c8f00d60</guid>
      <title>The new mad season?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Don't know if this is happening to you but I think our lack of a decent summer seems to be going to some people's heads. It is said that the most break downs of marriages and long term relationships happen after Christmas. I think this year's miserable attemptat a summer is taking its toll. All around me couples are having problems and I cannot understand why.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/09/someones-having-a-laugh.php</link>
      <guid>5b39e75a6705c465a12d056d4790614a</guid>
      <title>Someone's having a laugh</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This story &lt;a href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/business/7595884.stm" target="_blank"&gt;Housing dip 'slows divorce rate' &lt;/a&gt; tells us that the "Housing dip 'slows divorce rate'".  Someone is pulling my leg.  Have we got so bad that even fights with our spouses are subject to 'economic' conditions?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2008 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/09/an-african-refreshing-change.php</link>
      <guid>a12524e204238669c013b389b8eb71b9</guid>
      <title>An African Refreshing Change</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is the kind of story that warms the cockles of my heart.  It shows that despite some leaders (especially those in power) continue postering and plundering, there is a wind of change blowing through Africa - a change that will encourage the millions of the disporia enriching First World nations, to return and start to build a new Africa.  The second wind of change will surprise many including the Chinese.  The first wind of change refered to by the then British Prime Minister Harold Macmillan led to political independence.  The second refers to economic independence that surely must follow, albeit for many a bit late.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2008 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/09/workplace-unhappiness-growing.php</link>
      <guid>70da6bf74f9b4989d55fdcefbfdb5e3e</guid>
      <title>Workplace unhappiness 'growing'</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Article at &lt;a href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/business/7592050.stm"&gt;Workplace unhappiness 'growing'&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/06/wait-til-your-mum-gets-home.php</link>
      <guid>37404e356f82aeb80c8168fdd38acd04</guid>
      <title>Wait 'til your mum gets home...</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What's the world coming to?  Lots of my generation remembers the "wait 'til dad gets home" threat from Mum when you got you got yourself into trouble. Children all over the world quaked (and in some parts of the world, still do) when these words were said. I was one of the lucky/unlucky ones, Dad wasn't there and Mum dealt with it there and then. Don't know what's worse.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2008 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2008/02/valentines-day-is-bad-for-the-environment.php</link>
      <guid>688dbbc6809cbca2e83e40847716e227</guid>
      <title>Valentine's Day is Bad for the Environment</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Following on the heels that divorce is bad for the environment (if you don't know, because families then live in two residents), a discussion held in the office today reveals that additional fuel will be used to day as husbands throughout the country realise that the wife's 'we won't do anything for Valentines' was not to be taken literally and that the purchase of at least a card or even better a small pressie will lead to a pleasant evening.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2008 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2007/12/dreams-coming-true.php</link>
      <guid>075d11e097e3fba1e235e7d6e30507aa</guid>
      <title>Dreams coming true</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Well a few days after my renewed postings, I received a christmas card from my older brother.  That probably sounds like we are not in touch often which is true but a quick explanation is in order.He is actually my father's son from a previous marriage, a half brother in other words.  I hate the term myself anyway as growing up in Africa he is my brother and that's it, period. I hate it as much as the term half caste used for mixed race people.  But I digress.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2007 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2007/12/i-have-started-dreaming-again.php</link>
      <guid>940efe71cc94717eba6e4392d0ba81f9</guid>
      <title>I have started dreaming again</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have started dreaming again.  I mean the kind of dreaming that you do awake not the usually forgotten sleep process.  No, I mean those vivid, colourful day dreams that  make you feel good,  make you want to reach out and touch them.  You can call it hope if you want to.  Dreaming again and just in time too.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2007 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://benjyellis.net/blog/2007/12/abouttalking2myself.php</link>
      <guid>d0cf8ed3e1c3221ac6efde4f1cd370fd</guid>
      <title>About Talking2Myself Blog</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Happiness is not a permanent state. The natural state of man is not happiness but contentment - the proper balance of physical, emotional, mental and spiritual needs.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2007 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2017 16:10:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  </channel>
</rss>
